{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "a tooth \n\n---> four ___ ",
      "answer": "teeth",
      "explain": "- tooth -> teeth\n(irregular plural)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a name\n\n---> six ___",
      "answer": "names",
      "explain": "- name -> names",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a toy \n\n---> four ___ ",
      "answer": "toys",
      "explain": "- toy -> toys\nRemember: Nouns ending in y preceded by a vowel -> + s.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bag\n\n---> five ___",
      "answer": "bags",
      "explain": "- bag -> bags",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a buzz\n\n---> five ___",
      "answer": "buzzes",
      "explain": "- buzz -> buzzes\nRemember: Nouns ending in s, z, x, sh, and ch -> + es.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a toy\n\n---> five ___",
      "answer": "toys",
      "explain": "- toy -> toys\nRemember: Nouns ending in y preceded by a vowel -> + s.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a nose\n\n---> seven ___",
      "answer": "noses",
      "explain": "- nose -> noses",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wife\n\n---> two ____",
      "answer": "wives",
      "explain": "- wife -> wives\nSome nouns ending in f or fe -> changing f or fe to - ves. ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fox \n\n---> nine ___ ",
      "answer": "foxes",
      "explain": "- fox -> foxes\nRemember: Nouns ending in s, z, x, sh, and ch -> + es.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a family \n\n---> two ___ ",
      "answer": "families",
      "explain": "- family -> families\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "4"
    }
  ]
}